http://www.handylaundry.com/privacy-policy

Loading... Please wait...
Menu
CUSTOMER SERVICE - 800 - 263 - 5973
Compare (0 Item)
On Sale
The Handy Laundry Privacy Notice:
At Handy Laundry Inc., we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use information only to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience for you. We never reveal your personal information to anyone. WE DO NOT SELL OR TRADE OUR CUSTOMERS' NAMES OR ANY OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANYONE, EVER. What Information We Collect and Why. When you order, we ask for your name, E-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process your order and notify you of your order status. (Note: Giving us a fake E-mail address keeps us from confirming your order via E-mail. Please use a genuine email address if you wish to receive your order confirmation via E-mail.)
Personal Information
When you interact with us, we automatically receive and store certain types of information, such as the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”). This is statistical information used to monitor the usage of our website and for advertising purposes. This information does not include personal information.
How do we use the information? Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide HandyLaundry's visitors with a superior customized online experience. We use the customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems
How to update or correct your Information? You have the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided to us. Anytime during the online ordering process you can review, change, or delete the information that you have submitted. You can change any of your personal information in your account online at any time. We encourage you to update your information as soon as there are any changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past purchases, you cannot delete information associated with past purchases. Also, as a security measure we "back up" the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. As a result of this, you should not expect that all of your Personally Identifiable Information will be completely removed from our backed-up databases.
Marketing From time to time you may receive Handy Laundry special fliers via postal mail or e-mail notification of specials that may be of interest to you. E-mail recipients can opt-out from our e-mail listings by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided with every promotional email we send out. Registrants may also opt-out of receiving materials from us at any time by contacting us with such request.  Please contact us by telephone or postal mail at the number or address below Enclose a copy of your mailing label. Include your name, address, and other information as it appears on the mailing label, and indicate "Do not mail".
Cookies
As you browse handylaundry.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with handylaundry.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit Opt Out to opt out of AdRoll and their partners' targeted advertising.
Security
We implement a secure processing server on our site when collecting information to ensure a high level of security for your personal information entered such as bank details and credit card information.
Sign up for our newsletter
Name
Email
Company Info
Handy Laundry Products Corp.
Copyright 2020 HandyLaundry.com. All Rights Reserved. | Sitemap |
All prices are in USD.
